Kenneth Basjan

About Me

I am a software developer proficient in C#, Java, Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MERN Stack, and WordPress. I specialise in front-end development and own Weberu, an SMMA providing digital services to boost revenue and brand awareness for businesses around the world.

Work Experience



Weberu (SMMA)

Founder

November 2021 to Present.

Weberu is a social media marketing agency that offers services such as social media management, content creation, influencer marketing, and social media advertising.

- Developed and executed innovative social media campaigns for a range of clients, delivering measurable results and achieving client objectives.
- Built and managed a team of social media experts, overseeing all aspects of the business, including strategy, operations, and client management.



UVU UVU Africa: CapaCiTi Division

Software Developer Intern: ABSA Cohort January 2023 to Present

- Developing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, and Java, working with a team of experienced developers to create high-quality, user-friendly software solutions.
- Contributing to the development of multiple software projects, using agile development methodologies to deliver results efficiently and effectively.
- Demonstrating strong problem-solving skills and attention to detail, identifying and resolving issues quickly and efficiently to ensure that software solutions are delivered on time and to the highest quality standards.



//Software Developer //Entrepreneur

Contact Info

in linkedin.com/in/kenneth-basjan/

github.com/Abbbtle

o instagram.com/abbbtle/

kennethbasjan97@gmail.com

www.kennethbasjan.netlify.app

Relevant Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Java
- C#
- Python
- ReactJS
- Tailwind CSS
- BootStrap
- WordPress (Elementor)
- SEO
- Social Media
 Management
- Content Writing

Education History



National Diploma in Information Technology: Software Development

Central University of Technology: Bloemfontein Campus 2016 - 2019



Creative Business 101 for Videographers
ORMS Cape Town School for Photography
2021

Volunteer Work, Awards, Affiliations, and Interests



ISKCON Cape Town

2019 to Present

I serve at the ISKCON Cape Town temple as a brahmana priest, teacher / guide, musician, cook, and IT specialist. The goal of this project is to provide a safe space for young and old individuals who are are searching for God and need a space in order to; meditate, perform yoga, eat healthy vegetarian food, and dive deep into spiritual philosophy.

References

Miss Afika Maliwa

Company: (UVU Africa - CapaCiTi)

Role: Candidate Manager Phone: +27 78 692 2178

Email: afika.maliwa@capaciti.org.za

Mr Shadly Frans

Company: (UVU Africa - CapaCiTi)

Role: Mentor

Phone: +27 72 5757147

Email: shadly.frans@capaciti.org.za

Contact Info

in linkedin.com/in/kenneth-basjan/

github.com/Abbbtle

instagram.com/abbbtle/

kennethbasjan97@gmail.com

www.kennethbasjan.netlify.app

Mr Brandon September

Company: (UVU Africa - CapaCiTi)

Role: Mentor

Phone: +27 79 477 0660

Email:

brandon.september@capaciti.org.za

Mr Gokulesh Das

Role: Temple President

Company: (ISKCON Cape Town)

Phone: +27 72 416 0853